media-get.com 2017-12-10

# MediaGet

Mediaget IS COMMITTED TO PROTECT YOUR PRIVACY

The privacy is important to Mediaget. Our main goal is to protect your right to privacy. This Privacy Policy reveals what information we gather when you enter our website and explain why we collect this information.

By using the website and services offered through the website, downloading materials and software, you further agree to be bound by and to comply with this Privacy Statement. If you do not consent to the Privacy Policy and the practices given below, you should not use the website. Mediaget encourage you to read the Privacy Policy and to contact us as set forth below with any questions or comments.

Mediaget may alter this Privacy Policy at any time, at its sole discretion, without notice to you. The most current version is available through the website.

INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT

Mediaget collects information for a variety of purposes. Mediaget uses personal information in order to provide you with answers to your inquiries and questions. It may include name, e-mail address, telephone number, and more. Your personal information will not be revealed to any third parties without your consent, unless required otherwise by law.

Mediaget collects non-personal information which is gathered automatically. We collect statistics about the quantity of our visitors, their operating system and web browser, web pages entered on the website, time spent, traffic data, and IP address. This information can’t identify your personally. Mediaget uses this information internally in order to improve our services and products.

LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

We provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. These sites are not under control of Mediaget and operate independently. Mediaget is not responsible for any information on these websites. We encourage you to read their privacy policies before using the third party websites.

COOKIES

We use the so-called "cookies" to personalize your experience when using our website. Cookies serve to to identify customers, remember user preferences and registration information. The information we collect with cookies is not sold, rented, or shared with any outside parties.

EXCEPTIONAL DISCLOSURES

Mediaget may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or in some criminal cases if required to do so by law, or if we receive legal process.

Mediaget IS COMMITTED TO PROTECT YOUR PRIVACY

The privacy is important to Mediaget. Our main goal is to protect your right to privacy. This Privacy Policy reveals what information we gather when you enter our website and explain why we collect this information.

By using the website and services offered through the website, downloading materials and software, you further agree to be bound by and to comply with this Privacy Statement. If you do not consent to the Privacy Policy and the practices given below, you should not use the website. Mediaget encourage you to read the Privacy Policy and to contact us as set forth below with any questions or comments.

Mediaget may alter this Privacy Policy at any time, at its sole discretion, without notice to you. The most current version is available through the website.

INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT

Mediaget collects information for a variety of purposes. Mediaget uses personal information in order to provide you with answers to your inquiries and questions. It may include name, e-mail address, telephone number, and more. Your personal information will not be revealed to any third parties without your consent, unless required otherwise by law.

Mediaget collects non-personal information which is gathered automatically. We collect statistics about the quantity of our visitors, their operating system and web browser, web pages entered on the website, time spent, traffic data, and IP address. This information can’t identify your personally. Mediaget uses this information internally in order to improve our services and products.

LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

We provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. These sites are not under control of Mediaget and operate independently. Mediaget is not responsible for any information on these websites. We encourage you to read their privacy policies before using the third party websites.

COOKIES

We use the so-called "cookies" to personalize your experience when using our website. Cookies serve to to identify customers, remember user preferences and registration information. The information we collect with cookies is not sold, rented, or shared with any outside parties.

EXCEPTIONAL DISCLOSURES

Mediaget may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or in some criminal cases if required to do so by law, or if we receive legal process.
